1
00:00:02,586 --> 00:00:06,204
Friends S01E01: The Pilot

2
00:00:07,300 --> 00:00:11,830
<i>♪ So no one told you life was gonna be this way</i>

3
00:00:12,370 --> 00:00:16,540
<i>♪ Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A.</i>

4
00:00:15,390 --> 00:00:16,846

5
00:00:17,450 --> 00:00:21,260
<i>♪ It's like you're always stuck in second gear</i>

6
00:00:18,268 --> 00:00:19,633

7
00:00:21,720 --> 00:00:23,820
<i>♪ When it hasn't been your day,</i>

8
00:00:21,980 --> 00:00:23,641

9
00:00:23,820 --> 00:00:26,820
<i>♪ your week, your month, or even your year</i>

10
00:00:26,820 --> 00:00:30,780
<i>♪ but I'll be there for you</i>

11
00:00:27,444 --> 00:00:28,934

12
00:00:30,780 --> 00:00:32,610
<i>♪ When the rain starts to pour</i>

13
00:00:31,740 --> 00:00:33,446

14
00:00:32,610 --> 00:00:35,730
<i>♪ I'll be there for you</i>

15
00:00:35,702 --> 00:00:37,283

16
00:00:35,730 --> 00:00:37,570
<i>♪ Like I've been there before</i>

17
00:00:37,570 --> 00:00:40,580
<i>♪ I'll be there for you</i>

18
00:00:40,580 --> 00:00:44,240
<i>♪ 'Cause you're there for me too</i>

19
00:00:48,131 --> 00:00:49,792

20
00:00:49,966 --> 00:00:52,760
There's nothing to tell. It's just some guy I work with.

21
00:00:52,969 --> 00:00:55,137
Come on. You're going out with a guy.

22
00:00:55,305 --> 00:00:57,848
There's gotta be something wrong with him.

23
00:00:58,058 --> 00:00:59,933
So does he have a hump and a hair piece?

24
00:01:02,395 --> 00:01:03,771
Wait. Does he eat chalk?

25
00:01:05,023 --> 00:01:08,233
I don't want her to go through what I went through with Carl. Oh.

26
00:01:05,107 --> 00:01:06,096

27
00:01:08,443 --> 00:01:11,236
Okay, everybody relax. This is not even a date.

28
00:01:11,446 --> 00:01:14,406
It's just two people going out to dinner and not having sex.

29
00:01:14,616 --> 00:01:16,158
Sounds like a date to me.

30
00:01:16,618 --> 00:01:18,825

31
00:01:19,037 --> 00:01:21,872
I'm back in high school, in the middle of the cafeteria...

32
00:01:22,082 --> 00:01:25,417
...and I realize I'm totally naked.

33
00:01:25,627 --> 00:01:27,169
- Oh, yeah. - I've had that dream.

34
00:01:27,378 --> 00:01:31,465
Then I look down and I realize there is a phone...

35
00:01:32,050 --> 00:01:34,009
...there.

36
00:01:34,928 --> 00:01:36,845
- Instead of... - That's right!

37
00:01:37,055 --> 00:01:38,555
MONICA: That one, I've never had. PHOEBE: No.

38
00:01:38,723 --> 00:01:42,851
All of a sudden, the phone starts to ring.

39
00:01:43,061 --> 00:01:44,812
And it turns out it's my mother.

40
00:01:46,564 --> 00:01:50,859
Which is very, very weird because she never calls me.

41
00:01:51,153 --> 00:01:54,065

42
00:01:55,865 --> 00:01:57,783
Hi.

43
00:01:58,785 --> 00:02:01,954
This guy says "hello," I wanna kill myself.

44
00:02:02,247 --> 00:02:03,413
Are you okay, sweetie?

45
00:02:03,665 --> 00:02:08,335
I feel like someone grabbed my small intestine, pulled it out of my mouth...

46
00:02:08,503 --> 00:02:11,380
...and tied it around my neck. - Cookie?

47
00:02:13,383 --> 00:02:14,883
Carol moved her stuff out today.

48
00:02:15,093 --> 00:02:16,135
PHOEBE & JOEY: Oh.

49
00:02:16,302 --> 00:02:18,095
- Let me get you some coffee. - Thanks.

50
00:02:21,057 --> 00:02:22,808
Ew. Unh.

51
00:02:22,976 --> 00:02:26,937
No. No, don't! Stop cleansing my aura.

52
00:02:27,230 --> 00:02:29,773
Just leave my aura alone, okay?

53
00:02:31,776 --> 00:02:34,653
I'll be fine. All right? Really. I hope she'll be very happy.

54
00:02:34,821 --> 00:02:36,155
- No, you don't. - No, I don't.

55
00:02:36,322 --> 00:02:38,157
To hell with her. She left me!

56
00:02:39,200 --> 00:02:41,160
And you never knew she was a lesbian.

57
00:02:45,206 --> 00:02:47,374
No! Okay?

58
00:02:47,542 --> 00:02:50,335
Why does everyone keep fixating on that?

59
00:02:51,963 --> 00:02:54,756
She didn't know. How should I know?

60
00:02:56,593 --> 00:02:59,261
Sometimes I wish I was a lesbian.

61
00:03:00,889 --> 00:03:02,890
Did I say that out loud?

62
00:03:04,809 --> 00:03:08,896
All right, Ross. Look, you're feeling a lot of pain right now.

63
00:03:09,063 --> 00:03:11,481
You're angry. You're hurting.

64
00:03:11,733 --> 00:03:13,942
Can I tell you what the answer is?

65
00:03:14,152 --> 00:03:15,444
Strip joints!

66
00:03:17,614 --> 00:03:19,948
Come on, you're single. Have some hormones.

67
00:03:20,158 --> 00:03:22,451
See, but I don't want to be single, okay?

68
00:03:22,660 --> 00:03:25,829
I just wanna be married again.

69
00:03:29,959 --> 00:03:33,086
And I just want a million dollars!

70
00:03:34,214 --> 00:03:35,297
Rachel?

71
00:03:35,465 --> 00:03:38,175
Oh, God, Monica! Hi! Thank God!

72
00:03:38,343 --> 00:03:41,511
I went to your building and this guy with a hammer said...

73
00:03:41,679 --> 00:03:43,889
...that you might be here, and you are.

74
00:03:44,140 --> 00:03:47,643
- Can I get you some coffee? - Decaf.

75
00:03:48,228 --> 00:03:52,189
Okay, everybody, this is Rachel, another Lincoln High survivor.

76
00:03:52,440 --> 00:03:54,900
This is everybody. This is Chandler and Phoebe...

77
00:03:55,109 --> 00:03:57,361
...and Joey. And remember my brother, Ross?

78
00:03:57,528 --> 00:03:58,654
- Sure! - Hey.

79
00:03:58,821 --> 00:04:00,739
- Hi. - Oh, God.

80
00:04:08,539 --> 00:04:12,125
So you wanna tell us now, or are we waiting for four wet bridesmaids?

81
00:04:14,379 --> 00:04:19,341
Oh, God! Well, it started about a half-hour before the wedding.

82
00:04:19,509 --> 00:04:21,927
I was in this room with all the presents...

83
00:04:22,095 --> 00:04:23,929
...and I was looking at this gravy boat.

84
00:04:24,138 --> 00:04:27,557
This really gorgeous Limoges gravy boat.

85
00:04:27,725 --> 00:04:29,559
When all of a sudden... Sweet 'N Low?

86
00:04:29,727 --> 00:04:31,853
- I realized...

87
00:04:32,021 --> 00:04:35,941
...I was more turned on by this gravy boat than by Barry.

88
00:04:36,109 --> 00:04:39,152
Then I got really freaked out, and that's when it hit me:

89
00:04:39,320 --> 00:04:42,114
How much Barry looks like Mr. Potato Head.

90
00:04:42,532 --> 00:04:45,784
You know, I mean, I always knew he looked familiar, but...

91
00:04:47,954 --> 00:04:51,290
Anyway, I just had to get out of there, and I started wondering:

92
00:04:51,541 --> 00:04:55,127
"Why am I doing this?" And "Who am I doing this for?"

93
00:04:55,295 --> 00:04:59,673
Anyway, I just didn't know where to go, and I know you and I have drifted apart...

94
00:04:59,882 --> 00:05:02,718
...but you're the only person I know in the city.

95
00:05:02,927 --> 00:05:04,594
Who wasn't invited to the wedding.

96
00:05:04,971 --> 00:05:07,889
Oh, I was kind of hoping that wouldn't be an issue.

97
00:05:22,071 --> 00:05:24,573
I'm guessing he bought her the big pipe organ...

98
00:05:24,741 --> 00:05:27,200
...and she's really not happy about it.

99
00:05:28,453 --> 00:05:31,496
Daddy, I just... I can't marry him.

100
00:05:31,664 --> 00:05:33,332
I'm sorry.

101
00:05:33,499 --> 00:05:36,376
I just don't love him.

102
00:05:36,836 --> 00:05:39,504
Well, it matters to me.

103
00:05:42,008 --> 00:05:44,384
CHANDLER: She should not be wearing those pants.

104
00:05:45,595 --> 00:05:47,554
I say push her down the stairs.

105
00:05:47,764 --> 00:05:50,974
ALL: Push her down the stairs! Push her down the stairs!

106
00:05:55,229 --> 00:05:57,230
Come on, Daddy, listen to me!

107
00:05:57,440 --> 00:06:01,985
It's like all of my life, everyone's always told me, "You're a shoe!

108
00:06:02,153 --> 00:06:04,237
You're a shoe! You're a shoe! You're a shoe!"

109
00:06:04,447 --> 00:06:07,616
Then today I stopped and said, "What if I don't wanna be a shoe?

110
00:06:07,825 --> 00:06:10,994
What if I wanna be a purse? You know?

111
00:06:11,162 --> 00:06:12,954
Or a hat?"

112
00:06:13,873 --> 00:06:16,416
I don't want you to buy me a hat, I am a hat.

113
00:06:16,584 --> 00:06:18,794
It's a metaphor, Daddy!

114
00:06:20,546 --> 00:06:22,381
You can see where he'd have trouble.

115
00:06:25,635 --> 00:06:27,511
Look, Daddy, it's my life.

116
00:06:28,846 --> 00:06:31,306
Well, maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.

117
00:06:34,310 --> 00:06:36,812
I guess we've established she's staying with Monica.

118
00:06:38,898 --> 00:06:41,691
Well, maybe that's my decision.

119
00:06:42,276 --> 00:06:44,528
Well, maybe I don't need your money.

120
00:06:44,695 --> 00:06:46,947
Wait! Wait! I said maybe!

121
00:06:53,913 --> 00:06:56,123
Okay. Just breathe, that's it.

122
00:06:56,332 --> 00:06:58,792
Just try to think of nice, calm things.

123
00:06:59,001 --> 00:07:02,879
Raindrops on roses And whiskers on kittens

124
00:07:03,256 --> 00:07:07,217
Doorbells and sleigh bells And something with mittens

125
00:07:07,969 --> 00:07:11,346
La la la something With string

126
00:07:11,514 --> 00:07:13,390
I'm all better now.

127
00:07:15,184 --> 00:07:17,185
I helped.

128
00:07:18,855 --> 00:07:21,189
MONICA: Look, this is probably for the best, you know?

129
00:07:21,524 --> 00:07:24,067
Independence. Taking control of your life.

130
00:07:24,277 --> 00:07:28,613
And, hey, if you need anything, you can always come to Joey.

131
00:07:28,781 --> 00:07:32,200
Me and Chandler live right across the hall. And he's away a lot.

132
00:07:34,078 --> 00:07:36,621
Joey, stop hitting on her. It's her wedding day.

133
00:07:36,831 --> 00:07:38,790
What? Like there's a rule or something?

134
00:07:41,335 --> 00:07:44,880
Please don't do that again. It's a horrible sound.

135
00:07:45,047 --> 00:07:47,466
PAUL: Uh, it's Paul. - Buzz him in.

136
00:07:47,758 --> 00:07:50,051
- Who's Paul? - Paul, the wine guy, Paul?

137
00:07:50,261 --> 00:07:51,303
Maybe.

138
00:07:51,512 --> 00:07:54,806
Wait a minute. Your "not a real date" is with Paul, the wine guy?

139
00:07:55,016 --> 00:07:56,808
- He finally asked you out? - Yes.

140
00:07:56,976 --> 00:07:58,768
Ooh. This is a "Dear Diary" moment.

141
00:08:00,313 --> 00:08:01,813
Rach, wait, I can cancel.

142
00:08:02,064 --> 00:08:03,857
Please, no. Go, I'll be fine.

143
00:08:04,025 --> 00:08:07,736
Ross, are you okay? I mean, do you want me to stay?

144
00:08:08,613 --> 00:08:10,739
That'd be good.

145
00:08:11,115 --> 00:08:14,868
- Really? - No, go on! It's Paul, the wine guy.

146
00:08:18,706 --> 00:08:21,124
MONICA: Hi, come in. Paul, this is...

147
00:08:22,001 --> 00:08:24,544
...everybody. Everybody, this is Paul.

148
00:08:25,004 --> 00:08:26,046
JOEY: Paul, the wine guy.

149
00:08:26,255 --> 00:08:30,091
- Wine guy. - I didn't catch your name. Paul, was it?

150
00:08:30,510 --> 00:08:33,053
- Okay. Sit down. Two seconds. - Okay.

151
00:08:37,225 --> 00:08:40,310
Ooh, I just pulled out four eyelashes. That can't be good.

152
00:08:42,855 --> 00:08:44,731
So, Rachel, what are you up to tonight?

153
00:08:45,274 --> 00:08:49,110
Well, I was supposed to be headed for Aruba on my honeymoon...

154
00:08:49,278 --> 00:08:50,320
...so, nothing.

155
00:08:52,740 --> 00:08:54,950
Right. You're not even getting your honeymoon.

156
00:08:55,243 --> 00:08:59,204
God. No, no. Although, Aruba. Heh. This time of year? Eh.

157
00:08:59,372 --> 00:09:01,957
Talk about your...

158
00:09:02,124 --> 00:09:03,166
...big lizards.

159
00:09:07,964 --> 00:09:10,674
Anyway, if you don't feel like being alone tonight...

160
00:09:10,883 --> 00:09:13,718
...Joey and Chandler are helping me with my furniture.

161
00:09:13,886 --> 00:09:17,055
Yes, and we're very excited about it.

162
00:09:17,223 --> 00:09:20,559
Actually, thanks, but I'm just gonna hang out here tonight.

163
00:09:20,726 --> 00:09:22,769
- It's been a long day. - Oh, sure. Okay. Sure.

164
00:09:22,937 --> 00:09:24,271
Hey, Pheebs, you wanna help?

165
00:09:24,689 --> 00:09:26,648
Oh, I wish I could, but I don't want to.

166
00:09:34,865 --> 00:09:39,286
I'm supposed to attach a bracket-y thing to the side things...

167
00:09:39,453 --> 00:09:42,247
...using a bunch of these little worm guys.

168
00:09:43,416 --> 00:09:48,169
I have no bracket-y thing, I see no worm guys whatsoever...

169
00:09:48,337 --> 00:09:51,423
...and I cannot feel my legs.

170
00:09:53,009 --> 00:09:54,050
What's this?

171
00:09:54,260 --> 00:09:57,262
I have no idea.

172
00:09:59,140 --> 00:10:01,558
- Done with the bookcase. - All finished.

173
00:10:05,146 --> 00:10:06,938
This was Carol's favorite beer.

174
00:10:09,025 --> 00:10:11,693
She always drank it out of the can. I should have known.

175
00:10:11,861 --> 00:10:15,071
Hey. Ross, let me ask you a question.

176
00:10:15,239 --> 00:10:19,451
She got the furniture, the stereo, the good TV.

177
00:10:19,619 --> 00:10:20,660
What did you get?

178
00:10:20,995 --> 00:10:22,037
You guys.

179
00:10:22,204 --> 00:10:24,289
- Oh, God. Oh, my God. - You got screwed.

180
00:10:24,498 --> 00:10:28,793
- Oh, my God. - I know, I know. I'm such an idiot.

181
00:10:29,337 --> 00:10:33,882
I should've caught on when she went to the dentist four and five times a week.

182
00:10:34,050 --> 00:10:36,259
I mean, how clean can teeth get?

183
00:10:36,427 --> 00:10:38,845
My brother's going through that. He's such a mess.

184
00:10:39,013 --> 00:10:40,680
How did you get through it?

185
00:10:40,890 --> 00:10:44,392
He might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers.

186
00:10:44,560 --> 00:10:46,144
- Say her... - Leg?

187
00:10:46,312 --> 00:10:48,229
Heh. That's one way of going through it, yeah.

188
00:10:48,773 --> 00:10:50,315
Me, I went for the watch.

189
00:10:50,775 --> 00:10:52,651
- You actually broke her watch? - Mm.

190
00:10:53,277 --> 00:10:56,363
Barry, I'm sorry. I am so sorry.

191
00:10:56,614 --> 00:11:01,534
You probably think it's about making love with your socks on, but it isn't.

192
00:11:01,702 --> 00:11:04,537
It isn't, it's about me. And I...

193
00:11:11,587 --> 00:11:14,631
Hi. Machine cut me off again. Anyway...

194
00:11:16,425 --> 00:11:20,512
You know what's scary? What if there's only one woman for everybody?

195
00:11:20,721 --> 00:11:24,057
I mean, what if you get one woman, and that's it?

196
00:11:24,225 --> 00:11:29,104
Unfortunately, in my case, there was only one woman for her.

197
00:11:29,563 --> 00:11:32,816
What are you talking about? One woman.

198
00:11:33,401 --> 00:11:37,028
That's like saying there's only one flavor of ice cream for you.

199
00:11:37,196 --> 00:11:40,949
Let me tell you something, Ross. There's lots of flavors out there.

200
00:11:41,117 --> 00:11:45,578
There's rocky road and cookie dough and bing cherry vanilla.

201
00:11:46,205 --> 00:11:50,709
You can get them with jimmies or nuts or whipped cream.

202
00:11:50,960 --> 00:11:53,628
This is the best thing that ever happened to you.

203
00:11:53,796 --> 00:11:56,673
You got married. You were like, what, 8?

204
00:11:58,634 --> 00:12:02,637
Welcome back to the world. Grab a spoon.

205
00:12:02,805 --> 00:12:05,348
I honestly don't know if I'm hungry or horny.

206
00:12:05,808 --> 00:12:07,183
Then stay out of my freezer.

207
00:12:10,938 --> 00:12:14,357
Ever since she walked out on me, I...

208
00:12:14,692 --> 00:12:16,651
What? What?

209
00:12:16,819 --> 00:12:18,653
You wanna spell it out with noodles?

210
00:12:18,863 --> 00:12:22,449
No, it's more of a fifth date kind of revelation.

211
00:12:23,242 --> 00:12:26,286
Oh, so there's gonna be a fifth date?

212
00:12:27,830 --> 00:12:29,497
Isn't there?

213
00:12:29,707 --> 00:12:31,875
Yeah, yeah. I think there is.

214
00:12:33,711 --> 00:12:35,420
What were you gonna say?

215
00:12:37,047 --> 00:12:39,174
Well... Er, uh...

216
00:12:40,342 --> 00:12:42,552
Ever since she left me, um...

217
00:12:43,679 --> 00:12:46,973
...I haven't been able to perform...

218
00:12:47,224 --> 00:12:48,433
...sexually.

219
00:12:51,312 --> 00:12:52,812
Oh, God! Oh, God! I am so...

220
00:12:53,022 --> 00:12:54,230
- I'm so sorry. - It's okay.

221
00:12:54,440 --> 00:12:57,859
Being spit on is probably not what you need right now.

222
00:12:58,027 --> 00:12:59,736
Um...

223
00:13:00,112 --> 00:13:01,196
How long?

224
00:13:01,739 --> 00:13:02,822
Two years.

225
00:13:03,574 --> 00:13:05,283
Wow!

226
00:13:05,451 --> 00:13:08,411
I'm glad you smashed her watch.

227
00:13:10,372 --> 00:13:13,792
So you still think you might want that fifth date?

228
00:13:16,796 --> 00:13:18,338
Yeah.

229
00:13:18,506 --> 00:13:20,340
Yeah, I do.

230
00:13:21,550 --> 00:13:24,886
I, Joanie, take you, Charles, as my lawful husband.

231
00:13:25,221 --> 00:13:28,473
MINISTER: Do you take Joanie...? - Oh! See.

232
00:13:28,641 --> 00:13:33,853
But Joanie loved Chachi. That's the difference.

233
00:13:35,397 --> 00:13:36,773
"Grab a spoon."

234
00:13:37,107 --> 00:13:39,609
Do you know long it's been since I grabbed a spoon?

235
00:13:40,110 --> 00:13:42,946
Do the words, "Billy, don't be a hero," mean anything to you?

236
00:13:45,199 --> 00:13:49,702
You know, here's the thing. Even if I could get it together enough...

237
00:13:49,870 --> 00:13:52,413
...to ask a woman out...

238
00:13:52,873 --> 00:13:55,291
...who am I gonna ask?
我该约谁？

239
00:14:16,605 --> 00:14:17,981
Isn't this amazing?

240
00:14:18,148 --> 00:14:20,483
I mean, I have never made coffee before in my life.

241
00:14:20,651 --> 00:14:23,152
- That is amazing. - Congratulations.

242
00:14:23,362 --> 00:14:28,074
While you're on a roll, if you feel like you gotta make a Western omelet or something...

243
00:14:30,995 --> 00:14:34,455
Although, actually I'm really not that hungry this morning.

244
00:14:35,374 --> 00:14:36,708
- Good morning. MONICA: Good morning.

245
00:14:36,876 --> 00:14:38,501
- Morning.  - JOEY: Morning.

246
00:14:39,420 --> 00:14:41,588
- Morning. JOEY: Morning, Paul.

247
00:14:41,755 --> 00:14:44,966
- Hello, Paul. - Hi. Paul, is it?

248
00:14:49,096 --> 00:14:51,848
MONICA: I had a really great time last night.

249
00:14:52,016 --> 00:14:53,892
PAUL: Thank you. Thank you so much.

250
00:14:54,602 --> 00:14:57,478
- We'll talk later, okay? - Yeah.

251
00:15:02,151 --> 00:15:03,985
Thank you.

252
00:15:09,825 --> 00:15:12,619
That wasn't a real date.

253
00:15:13,329 --> 00:15:16,164
What the hell do you do on a real date?

254
00:15:17,041 --> 00:15:20,501
- Shut up and put my table back. JOEY: Okay.

255
00:15:20,669 --> 00:15:22,545
All right, kids, I gotta get to work.

256
00:15:22,755 --> 00:15:28,259
If I don't input those numbers, it doesn't make much of a difference.

257
00:15:31,305 --> 00:15:33,431
So, like, you guys all have jobs?

258
00:15:34,224 --> 00:15:35,892
Yeah, we all have jobs.

259
00:15:36,101 --> 00:15:38,728
See, that's how we buy stuff.

260
00:15:40,356 --> 00:15:41,648
Yeah, I'm an actor.

261
00:15:41,857 --> 00:15:44,067
Wow. Would I have seen you in anything?

262
00:15:44,276 --> 00:15:46,611
Oh, I doubt it. Mostly regional work.

263
00:15:46,820 --> 00:15:50,406
Unless you happened to catch the Wee One's production of Pinocchio.

264
00:15:50,658 --> 00:15:53,201
"Look, Geppeto. I'm a real live boy."

265
00:15:56,038 --> 00:15:57,747
I will not take this abuse.

266
00:15:57,998 --> 00:15:59,916
You're right. I'm sorry.

267
00:16:00,334 --> 00:16:03,044
Once I was a wooden boy A little wooden boy

268
00:16:07,132 --> 00:16:09,467
MONICA: So how are you doing today? Did you sleep okay?

269
00:16:09,677 --> 00:16:13,012
Did you talk to Barry? I can't stop smiling.

270
00:16:13,806 --> 00:16:17,684
I can see that. You look like you slept with a hanger in your mouth.

271
00:16:22,940 --> 00:16:26,401
I know. He's just so...

272
00:16:26,568 --> 00:16:28,111
Remember you and Tony De Marco?

273
00:16:28,320 --> 00:16:32,323
- Oh, yeah. - Well, it's like that. With feelings.

274
00:16:33,200 --> 00:16:34,867
Oh, wow, are you in trouble!

275
00:16:35,536 --> 00:16:39,330
Okay, okay. I am just going to get up, go to work...

276
00:16:39,498 --> 00:16:42,208
...and not think about him all day.

277
00:16:42,376 --> 00:16:45,336
Or else I'm just gonna get up and go to work.

278
00:16:45,504 --> 00:16:47,130
- Oh, wish me luck! - What for?

279
00:16:47,339 --> 00:16:50,633
I'm gonna go get one of those job things.

280
00:16:58,600 --> 00:17:01,227
- Hey, Monica. - Hey, Franny. Welcome back.

281
00:17:01,395 --> 00:17:02,895
How was Florida?

282
00:17:03,063 --> 00:17:04,397
You had sex, didn't you?

283
00:17:06,275 --> 00:17:07,316
How do you do that?

284
00:17:08,444 --> 00:17:12,238
- So, who? - You know Paul?

285
00:17:12,781 --> 00:17:14,365
Paul, the wine guy?

286
00:17:14,533 --> 00:17:16,117
Oh, yeah, I know Paul.

287
00:17:18,662 --> 00:17:21,164
You mean, you know Paul like I know Paul?

288
00:17:21,373 --> 00:17:23,666
Are you kidding? I take credit for Paul.

289
00:17:23,834 --> 00:17:27,962
Before me, there was no snap in his turtle for two years.

290
00:17:31,216 --> 00:17:33,760
Of course it was a line.

291
00:17:34,178 --> 00:17:36,846
Why? Why would anybody do something like that?

292
00:17:37,056 --> 00:17:40,308
We're looking for an answer more sophisticated than:

293
00:17:40,476 --> 00:17:42,393
"To get you into bed."

294
00:17:43,353 --> 00:17:45,021
Is it me?

295
00:17:45,189 --> 00:17:48,733
Is it like I have some sort of beacon that only dogs...

296
00:17:48,901 --> 00:17:51,527
...and men with severe emotional problems can hear?

297
00:17:51,737 --> 00:17:53,654
All right, come here. Give me your feet.

298
00:18:01,163 --> 00:18:02,997
I just thought he was nice, you know?

299
00:18:05,876 --> 00:18:08,336
I can't believe you didn't know it was a line.

300
00:18:13,217 --> 00:18:14,258
Guess what.

301
00:18:14,426 --> 00:18:16,219
- You got a job? - Are you kidding?

302
00:18:16,386 --> 00:18:18,054
I'm trained for nothing.

303
00:18:19,890 --> 00:18:21,933
I was laughed out of 12 interviews today.

304
00:18:22,101 --> 00:18:23,643
Yet you're surprisingly upbeat.

305
00:18:23,852 --> 00:18:27,355
Well, you would be too if you found Joan and David boots on sale...

306
00:18:27,523 --> 00:18:29,273
...50 percent off.

307
00:18:29,483 --> 00:18:31,275
Oh, how well you know me.

308
00:18:32,945 --> 00:18:35,363
They're my new "I don't need a job or my parents.

309
00:18:35,614 --> 00:18:37,782
I've got great boots" boots.

310
00:18:39,159 --> 00:18:41,369
- How'd you pay for them? - Uh, credit card.

311
00:18:41,912 --> 00:18:43,579
And who pays for that?

312
00:18:44,248 --> 00:18:46,332
Um, my father.

313
00:18:48,919 --> 00:18:51,087
You can't live off your parents your whole life.

314
00:18:51,296 --> 00:18:54,966
I know that. That's why I was getting married.

315
00:18:55,342 --> 00:18:58,344
Give her a break. It's hard being on your own for the first time.

316
00:18:58,512 --> 00:19:00,012
- Thank you. - You're welcome.

317
00:19:00,180 --> 00:19:02,890
I remember when I first came to this city, I was 14.

318
00:19:03,058 --> 00:19:05,935
My mom had killed herself and my stepdad was back in prison.

319
00:19:06,103 --> 00:19:08,146
And I got here, and I didn't know anybody.

320
00:19:08,313 --> 00:19:11,691
I ended up living with this albino guy who was cleaning windshields...

321
00:19:11,859 --> 00:19:15,653
...outside Port Authority. And then he killed himself.

322
00:19:16,405 --> 00:19:20,241
And then I found aromatherapy. So believe me, I know exactly how you feel.

323
00:19:24,371 --> 00:19:27,123
The word you're looking for is:

324
00:19:27,708 --> 00:19:28,958
"Anyway..."

325
00:19:33,130 --> 00:19:34,255
All right. You ready?

326
00:19:34,423 --> 00:19:36,132
- I don't think so. ROSS: Oh, come on.

327
00:19:36,466 --> 00:19:37,884
Cut. Cut.

328
00:19:38,093 --> 00:19:41,053
ALL: Cut, cut, cut.

329
00:19:42,681 --> 00:19:45,600
ROSS: Hey. MONICA: All right.

330
00:19:45,851 --> 00:19:47,560
Welcome to the real world.

331
00:19:47,769 --> 00:19:50,521
It sucks. You're gonna love it.

332
00:19:57,446 --> 00:20:00,781
Well, that's it. You gonna crash on the couch?

333
00:20:00,991 --> 00:20:04,327
- No. No, I gotta go home sometime. - Are you gonna be okay?

334
00:20:04,494 --> 00:20:05,995
Yeah.

335
00:20:07,039 --> 00:20:08,915
Look what I just found on the floor.

336
00:20:11,210 --> 00:20:12,460
What?

337
00:20:12,920 --> 00:20:14,420
That's Paul's watch.

338
00:20:14,588 --> 00:20:16,672
You can just put it back where you found it.

339
00:20:18,300 --> 00:20:21,761
Oh, boy. All right. Good night, everybody.

340
00:20:21,929 --> 00:20:22,970
ROSS & RACHEL: Good night.

341
00:20:31,480 --> 00:20:33,147
- Hmm.  - Hmm.

342
00:20:34,274 --> 00:20:35,524
- Oh, sorry. - No. Oh, no. Go.

343
00:20:35,692 --> 00:20:37,652
- No, have it, really. - Split it?

344
00:20:37,819 --> 00:20:39,820
- Okay. - Okay.

345
00:20:41,740 --> 00:20:42,782
Thanks.

346
00:20:43,492 --> 00:20:47,078
You probably didn't know this, but back in high school I had...

347
00:20:47,246 --> 00:20:49,080
...a major crush on you.

348
00:20:50,540 --> 00:20:51,707
I knew.

349
00:20:52,084 --> 00:20:54,335
You did? Oh.

350
00:20:55,128 --> 00:20:58,130
I figured you thought I was Monica's geeky older brother.

351
00:20:58,882 --> 00:21:00,883
- I did. - Oh.

352
00:21:05,514 --> 00:21:07,348
Listen, do you think...

353
00:21:07,516 --> 00:21:11,018
And try not to let my vulnerability become any kind of a factor here.

354
00:21:13,105 --> 00:21:16,983
Do you think it would be okay if I ask you out sometime, maybe?

355
00:21:18,235 --> 00:21:20,069
Yeah.

356
00:21:20,529 --> 00:21:21,821
Maybe.

357
00:21:22,823 --> 00:21:24,657
Okay.

358
00:21:29,413 --> 00:21:31,872
Okay, maybe I will.

359
00:21:35,836 --> 00:21:37,962
- Good night. - Good night.

360
00:21:51,518 --> 00:21:53,227
See you.

361
00:21:53,729 --> 00:21:54,770
ROSS: Mm-hm.

362
00:21:54,938 --> 00:21:57,356
Wait, wait. Hey, what's with you?

363
00:21:59,651 --> 00:22:02,320
I just grabbed a spoon.

364
00:22:10,495 --> 00:22:11,954
Can't believe what I'm hearing.

365
00:22:12,205 --> 00:22:13,873
I can't believe What I'm hearing here

366
00:22:14,041 --> 00:22:16,250
- What? I said you had... - What? I said you had...

367
00:22:17,294 --> 00:22:19,754
- Would you stop? - Oh, was I doing it again?

368
00:22:19,963 --> 00:22:21,797
ALL: Yes.

369
00:22:22,841 --> 00:22:24,842
WOMAN: Would anybody like more coffee?

370
00:22:26,720 --> 00:22:29,180
Did you make it or are you just serving it?

371
00:22:29,348 --> 00:22:32,641
- I'm just serving it. CHANDLER: I'll have a cup of coffee.

372
00:22:33,101 --> 00:22:34,352
Kids, new dream.

373
00:22:35,103 --> 00:22:38,439
I'm in Las Vegas. I'm Liza Minnelli.

