1
00:00:02,877 --> 00:00:04,294
What you guys don't understand is...

2
00:00:04,504 --> 00:00:07,548
...for us, kissing is as important as any part of it.

3
00:00:07,924 --> 00:00:09,508
Yeah, right.

4
00:00:11,970 --> 00:00:13,095
You serious?

5
00:00:14,139 --> 00:00:15,097
Oh, yeah.

6
00:00:15,306 --> 00:00:17,683
Everything you need to know is in that first kiss.

7
00:00:17,892 --> 00:00:19,768
- Absolutely. - Yeah, I think, for us...

8
00:00:19,978 --> 00:00:22,021
...kissing is pretty much like an opening act.

9
00:00:22,230 --> 00:00:24,773
I mean, it's like the stand-up comedian you have to sit through...

10
00:00:24,983 --> 00:00:27,109
...before Pink Floyd comes out.

11
00:00:30,363 --> 00:00:33,699
Yeah, and it's not that we don't like the comedian.

12
00:00:33,908 --> 00:00:37,077
It's just that that's not...

13
00:00:37,287 --> 00:00:39,288
...why we bought the ticket.

14
00:00:40,707 --> 00:00:42,207
See, the problem is, though...

15
00:00:42,417 --> 00:00:45,002
...after the concert's over, no matter how great the show was...

16
00:00:45,211 --> 00:00:48,672
...you girls are always looking for the comedian again.

17
00:00:48,882 --> 00:00:50,883
I mean, we're in the car, we're fighting traffic...

18
00:00:51,092 --> 00:00:53,844
...basically just trying to stay awake.

19
00:00:55,889 --> 00:00:58,932
Yeah, well, word of advice: Bring back the comedian.

20
00:00:59,142 --> 00:01:00,893
Otherwise, you're gonna find yourself...

21
00:01:01,102 --> 00:01:03,687
...sitting at home listening to that album alone.

22
00:01:08,443 --> 00:01:10,778
Are we still talking about sex?

23
00:01:12,281 --> 00:01:14,146
Friends S01E02: The One with the Sonogram at the End

24
00:01:23,000 --> 00:01:24,991

25
00:01:27,087 --> 00:01:29,078

26
00:01:31,049 --> 00:01:33,040

27
00:01:37,347 --> 00:01:39,338

28
00:01:41,435 --> 00:01:43,426

29
00:01:45,606 --> 00:01:47,597

30
00:02:02,331 --> 00:02:03,696

31
00:02:05,333 --> 00:02:07,209
ROSS: No, it's good. It is good.

32
00:02:07,418 --> 00:02:11,088
It's just that, doesn't she seem a little angry?

33
00:02:11,297 --> 00:02:13,006
Well, she has issues.

34
00:02:13,175 --> 00:02:14,540

35
00:02:14,717 --> 00:02:16,218
Does she?

36
00:02:16,427 --> 00:02:18,637
He's out banging other women over the head with a club...

37
00:02:18,847 --> 00:02:22,683
...while she sits at home trying to get the mastodon smell out of the carpet.

38
00:02:22,934 --> 00:02:25,978
Marsha, see, these are cave people.

39
00:02:27,021 --> 00:02:29,356
Okay, they have issues like:

40
00:02:29,566 --> 00:02:33,569
"Gee, that glacier's getting kind of close." See?

41
00:02:33,778 --> 00:02:35,863
Speaking of issues, isn't that your ex-wife?

42
00:02:36,072 --> 00:02:38,740
- No, no. - Yes, it is. Carol, hi.

43
00:02:38,950 --> 00:02:40,492
ROSS: Okay. Yes. Yes, it is.

44
00:02:40,702 --> 00:02:43,078
How about I'll catch up with you in the Ice Age?

45
00:02:43,246 --> 00:02:44,531

46
00:02:45,874 --> 00:02:47,865

47
00:02:50,712 --> 00:02:52,748

48
00:02:57,969 --> 00:02:59,761
- Hi. - Hi.

49
00:03:06,936 --> 00:03:08,520
So...

50
00:03:09,355 --> 00:03:11,190
You look great.

51
00:03:11,983 --> 00:03:13,066
I hate that.

52
00:03:14,068 --> 00:03:17,362
Sorry. Thanks. You look good too.

53
00:03:17,572 --> 00:03:20,490
Well, you know, in here, anyone who...

54
00:03:22,076 --> 00:03:23,327
...stands erect...

55
00:03:26,748 --> 00:03:28,624
- So, what's new? Still a... - A lesbian?

56
00:03:28,833 --> 00:03:30,417
Well...

57
00:03:31,502 --> 00:03:32,961
You never know.

58
00:03:33,171 --> 00:03:35,214
How's, um...? How's the family?

59
00:03:35,715 --> 00:03:37,799
Marty's still totally paranoid.

60
00:03:38,009 --> 00:03:41,094
- Oh, and... - Carol, why are you here, Carol?

61
00:03:42,513 --> 00:03:45,224
- I'm pregnant. - Pregnant.

62
00:03:52,857 --> 00:03:56,235
Oh. Looks like she didn't leave in such a hurry after all.

63
00:03:56,611 --> 00:03:58,695
I think this is the episode of Three's Company...

64
00:03:58,905 --> 00:04:01,198
...where's there's some kind of misunderstanding.

65
00:04:04,118 --> 00:04:06,536
Then I've already seen this one.

66
00:04:08,081 --> 00:04:09,998
Are you through with that? Thanks.

67
00:04:10,208 --> 00:04:12,626
Yeah, sorry, the swallowing slowed me down.

68
00:04:14,128 --> 00:04:15,921
Whose little ball of paper is this?

69
00:04:16,130 --> 00:04:17,172
Oh, that would be mine.

70
00:04:17,382 --> 00:04:19,841
See, I wrote a note to myself, then I didn't need it.

71
00:04:20,051 --> 00:04:22,261
So I balled it up and now I wish I was dead.

72
00:04:24,847 --> 00:04:27,724
She already fluffed that pillow. Monica, you know, you already fluffed...

73
00:04:27,934 --> 00:04:29,768
But it's fine.

74
00:04:30,228 --> 00:04:31,186
Look, I'm sorry.

75
00:04:31,396 --> 00:04:33,855
I don't want to give them any more ammunition than they have.

76
00:04:34,065 --> 00:04:35,941
Yes, we know how cruel a parent can be...

77
00:04:36,150 --> 00:04:39,278
...about the flatness of a child's pillow.

78
00:04:39,821 --> 00:04:42,281
Monica? Hi. Um...

79
00:04:42,865 --> 00:04:45,325
Monica, um, you're scaring me.

80
00:04:46,661 --> 00:04:50,247
I mean, you're, like, all chaotic and twirly, you know?

81
00:04:50,456 --> 00:04:51,665
Not in a good way.

82
00:04:53,543 --> 00:04:54,710
Yeah, calm down.

83
00:04:54,919 --> 00:04:59,214
You don't see Ross getting all chaotic and twirly every time they come.

84
00:04:59,424 --> 00:05:03,302
That's because, as far as my parents are concerned, Ross can do no wrong. 

85
00:05:03,511 --> 00:05:05,554
You see, he's the prince.

86
00:05:05,763 --> 00:05:09,141
Apparently they had some big ceremony before I was born. 

87
00:05:10,893 --> 00:05:12,561
Ew, ew, ew. 

88
00:05:12,812 --> 00:05:15,439
- What? - Ugly Naked Guy got a ThighMaster.

89
00:05:18,067 --> 00:05:19,526
Ew.

90
00:05:20,528 --> 00:05:23,322
- Has anybody seen my engagement ring? - Yeah, it's beautiful.

91
00:05:28,870 --> 00:05:30,370
Oh, God. Oh, God.

92
00:05:30,580 --> 00:05:34,041
- Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God. - No, don't touch that. 

93
00:05:36,461 --> 00:05:40,714
Oh, like I wasn't dreading tomorrow enough having to give it back to him.

94
00:05:40,965 --> 00:05:42,716
"Hi, Barry, remember me? I'm the girl... 

95
00:05:42,925 --> 00:05:46,094
...that stomped on your heart in front of your entire family"

96
00:05:46,304 --> 00:05:49,639
Oh, God. Now I'm gonna have to return the ring, without the ring...

97
00:05:49,849 --> 00:05:52,726
...which makes it so much harder.

98
00:05:53,603 --> 00:05:55,562
Easy, Rach, we'll find it. Won't we? 

99
00:05:55,772 --> 00:05:57,481
- Oh, yeah. MONICA: Okay, look.

100
00:06:00,151 --> 00:06:01,693
When did you have it on last?

101
00:06:01,903 --> 00:06:04,237
Doy. Probably right before she lost it.

102
00:06:06,574 --> 00:06:09,242
You don't get a lot of "doy" these days.

103
00:06:10,870 --> 00:06:13,705
I know I had it this morning.

104
00:06:13,915 --> 00:06:16,792
I know I had it when I was in the kitchen with...

105
00:06:17,001 --> 00:06:18,627
Dinah?

106
00:06:21,297 --> 00:06:24,049
Oh, don't be mad.

107
00:06:24,467 --> 00:06:26,885
- You didn't. - Oh, I'm sorry.

108
00:06:27,095 --> 00:06:29,388
I gave you one job.

109
00:06:30,598 --> 00:06:33,683
Oh, but look how straight those noodles are.

110
00:06:34,477 --> 00:06:38,522
Monica, you know that's not how you look for an engagement ring in a lasagna.

111
00:06:41,025 --> 00:06:42,609
I just can't do it.

112
00:06:43,861 --> 00:06:45,153
Boys?

113
00:06:46,030 --> 00:06:47,697
We're going in.

114
00:06:56,040 --> 00:06:57,416
Hi.

115
00:06:58,334 --> 00:07:00,544
Oh, that is not a happy "hi."

116
00:07:00,753 --> 00:07:02,254
Carol's pregnant.

117
00:07:02,463 --> 00:07:04,047
Oh, I found it.

118
00:07:06,217 --> 00:07:09,302
Well, what...? What?

119
00:07:09,720 --> 00:07:11,054
Yeah.

120
00:07:12,014 --> 00:07:13,348
Do that for another two hours...

121
00:07:13,558 --> 00:07:16,560
...you might be where I am right about now.

122
00:07:17,603 --> 00:07:20,814
Kind of puts that whole pillow thing in perspective, huh, Mon?

123
00:07:23,151 --> 00:07:25,152
Well, now, how do you fit into this whole thing?

124
00:07:25,361 --> 00:07:28,447
Well, Carol says she and Susan want me to be involved.

125
00:07:28,656 --> 00:07:33,285
But if I'm not comfortable with it, I don't have to be involved.

126
00:07:33,578 --> 00:07:35,495
Basically, it's totally up to me.

127
00:07:35,705 --> 00:07:37,914
She is so great. I miss her.

128
00:07:43,171 --> 00:07:44,546
What does she mean by "involved"?

129
00:07:44,755 --> 00:07:47,340
I mean, presumably, the biggest part of your job is done.

130
00:07:49,594 --> 00:07:52,179
Anyway, they want me to go down to this...

131
00:07:52,388 --> 00:07:54,806
...sonogram thing with them tomorrow.

132
00:07:55,016 --> 00:07:56,057
So, what are you gonna do?

133
00:07:56,267 --> 00:07:58,310
I have no idea.

134
00:07:58,519 --> 00:08:02,147
No matter what I do, though, I'm still gonna be a father.

135
00:08:12,241 --> 00:08:13,909
Well, this is still ruined, right?

136
00:08:19,832 --> 00:08:23,835
Oh. Martha Lugwin's daughter is gonna call you.

137
00:08:25,505 --> 00:08:28,381
Mm. What's that curry taste?

138
00:08:28,841 --> 00:08:30,133
Curry.

139
00:08:31,344 --> 00:08:32,802
Mm.

140
00:08:34,472 --> 00:08:37,557
I think they're great. I really do.

141
00:08:37,767 --> 00:08:38,725
You remember the Lugwins?

142
00:08:38,935 --> 00:08:40,810
The big one had a thing for you, didn't she?

143
00:08:41,020 --> 00:08:42,771
They all had a thing for him.

144
00:08:43,648 --> 00:08:44,731
Oh, Mom.

145
00:08:44,941 --> 00:08:47,025
I'm sorry. Why is this girl going to call me?

146
00:08:47,235 --> 00:08:51,738
Oh, she just graduated, and she wants to be something in cooking or food...

147
00:08:51,948 --> 00:08:53,073
...or I don't know.

148
00:08:53,282 --> 00:08:55,659
Anyway, I told her you had a restaurant, so...

149
00:08:55,868 --> 00:08:58,537
No, Mom. I don't have a restaurant. I work in a restaurant. 

150
00:08:58,746 --> 00:09:01,414
Well, they don't have to know that.

151
00:09:04,669 --> 00:09:06,962
Ross, could you come and help me with the spaghetti.

152
00:09:07,171 --> 00:09:08,129
Yes.

153
00:09:08,339 --> 00:09:10,590
Oh, we're having spaghetti. That's...

154
00:09:10,800 --> 00:09:12,259
...easy.

155
00:09:14,262 --> 00:09:17,347
I know this is going to sound unbelievably selfish on my part...

156
00:09:17,557 --> 00:09:20,767
...but were you planning on bringing up the whole baby/lesbian thing?

157
00:09:20,977 --> 00:09:23,687
Because I think it might take some of the heat off me.

158
00:09:26,816 --> 00:09:30,652
What that Rachel did to her life. We ran into her parents at the club.

159
00:09:30,861 --> 00:09:32,821
They were not playing very well.

160
00:09:33,030 --> 00:09:35,282
I'm not gonna tell you what they spent on that wedding...

161
00:09:35,658 --> 00:09:38,034
...but $40,000 is a lot of money.

162
00:09:40,997 --> 00:09:44,666
Well, at least she had the chance to leave a man at the altar.

163
00:09:47,837 --> 00:09:50,589
- What's that supposed to mean? - Nothing.

164
00:09:50,798 --> 00:09:54,092
- It's an expression. - No, it's not.

165
00:09:54,302 --> 00:09:55,468
Don't listen to your mother.

166
00:09:55,678 --> 00:09:57,637
You're independent and you always have been.

167
00:09:57,847 --> 00:10:00,307
Even when you were a kid, and you were chubby...

168
00:10:00,516 --> 00:10:03,351
...and you had no friends, you were just fine.

169
00:10:05,146 --> 00:10:08,273
You'd read alone in your room. And your puzzles...

170
00:10:11,819 --> 00:10:15,780
Look, there are people, like Ross, who need to shoot for the stars. 

171
00:10:15,990 --> 00:10:18,825
With his museum and his papers getting published.

172
00:10:19,035 --> 00:10:21,286
Other people are satisfied with staying where they are.

173
00:10:21,495 --> 00:10:25,165
I'm telling you, these are the people who never get cancer.

174
00:10:28,085 --> 00:10:32,213
And I read about these women trying to have it all, and I thank God...

175
00:10:32,423 --> 00:10:35,425
...our little Harmonica doesn't seem to have that problem.

176
00:10:38,137 --> 00:10:40,847
So, Ross, what's going on with you?

177
00:10:41,891 --> 00:10:45,977
Any stories? No news, no little anecdotes to share with the folks? 

178
00:10:46,187 --> 00:10:47,270
Okay, okay.

179
00:10:49,273 --> 00:10:54,027
Ahem. Look, I, uh... I realize you guys have been wondering...

180
00:10:54,236 --> 00:10:56,863
...what exactly happened between Carol and me.

181
00:10:57,073 --> 00:10:58,865
And so, well, here's the deal.

182
00:11:01,911 --> 00:11:03,370
Carol's a lesbian.

183
00:11:05,623 --> 00:11:07,874
She's living with a woman named Susan.

184
00:11:09,835 --> 00:11:12,921
She's pregnant with my child.

185
00:11:13,464 --> 00:11:16,466
And she and Susan are going to raise the baby.

186
00:11:20,680 --> 00:11:22,180
And you knew about this?

187
00:11:31,608 --> 00:11:34,270

188
00:11:36,904 --> 00:11:38,655
Your folks are really that bad, huh?

189
00:11:39,782 --> 00:11:42,325
Well, you know, these people are pros.

190
00:11:44,620 --> 00:11:47,163
They know what they're doing. They take their time.

191
00:11:47,373 --> 00:11:50,041
They get the job done.

192
00:11:51,836 --> 00:11:55,004
Boy, I know they say that you can't change your parents.

193
00:11:55,214 --> 00:11:58,341
Boy, if you could, I'd want yours. 

194
00:12:00,302 --> 00:12:01,928
Must pee.

195
00:12:03,013 --> 00:12:04,764
You know, it's even worse when you're twins.

196
00:12:04,974 --> 00:12:07,142
- You're a twin? - Oh, yeah. We don't speak. 

197
00:12:07,351 --> 00:12:10,145
She's like this high-powered, driven, career-type.

198
00:12:10,479 --> 00:12:12,313
- What does she do? - She's a waitress. 

199
00:12:14,567 --> 00:12:17,527
All right. You guys, I kind of gotta clean up now.

200
00:12:17,737 --> 00:12:20,613
Chandler, you're an only child, right? You don't have any of this.

201
00:12:20,823 --> 00:12:24,159
Well, no, although I did have an imaginary friend...

202
00:12:24,368 --> 00:12:26,244
...who my parents actually preferred.

203
00:12:28,539 --> 00:12:30,582
RACHEL: Hit the lights, please.

204
00:12:37,506 --> 00:12:38,923
How long was I in there?

205
00:12:40,718 --> 00:12:41,885
I'm just cleaning up.

206
00:12:42,636 --> 00:12:45,472
Oh, do you, uh...? Do you need any help?

207
00:12:45,681 --> 00:12:48,349
Um, okay, sure. Thanks.

208
00:12:54,231 --> 00:12:55,690
Anyway...

209
00:12:56,358 --> 00:12:59,194
So you nervous about Barry tomorrow?

210
00:12:59,403 --> 00:13:02,155
- Oh, a little. - Mm-hm.

211
00:13:03,282 --> 00:13:05,200
- A lot. - Mm-hm.

212
00:13:05,910 --> 00:13:08,453
So got any advice?

213
00:13:08,662 --> 00:13:11,748
You know, as someone who's recently been dumped.

214
00:13:13,000 --> 00:13:16,461
Well, you may want to steer clear of the word "dumped."

215
00:13:17,880 --> 00:13:22,091
Chances are he's going to be this broken shell of a man. You know?

216
00:13:22,301 --> 00:13:26,346
So you should try not to look too terrific. I know it'll be hard.

217
00:13:29,850 --> 00:13:34,229
Or, you know, hey, I'll go down there, and I'll give Barry back his ring.

218
00:13:34,438 --> 00:13:38,775
And you can go with Carol and Susan to the OB-GYN.

219
00:13:41,028 --> 00:13:43,488
You've got Carol tomorrow.

220
00:13:44,323 --> 00:13:46,282
When did it get so complicated?

221
00:13:46,492 --> 00:13:47,784
Got me.

222
00:13:48,452 --> 00:13:51,079
- Remember when we were in high school? - Yeah.

223
00:13:51,288 --> 00:13:53,790
I mean, didn't you think you' were gonna meet someone...

224
00:13:53,999 --> 00:13:56,543
...fall in love, and that'd be it?

225
00:14:01,590 --> 00:14:03,508
- Ross? - Yes, yes.

226
00:14:05,135 --> 00:14:08,844
Oh. Man. I never thought I'd be here.

227
00:14:16,730 --> 00:14:18,398
Me neither.

228
00:14:35,624 --> 00:14:37,876
Hi. Sorry I'm late. I got stuck at work.

229
00:14:38,085 --> 00:14:41,546
There was this big dinosaur thing. Anyway...

230
00:14:42,631 --> 00:14:44,173
Hi.

231
00:14:44,758 --> 00:14:47,886
- Ross, you remember Susan. - How could I forget?

232
00:14:48,095 --> 00:14:49,262
Ross.

233
00:14:49,471 --> 00:14:52,098
Hello, Susan. Good shake, good shake.

234
00:14:54,018 --> 00:14:56,728
So, uh, we're just waiting for?

235
00:14:56,937 --> 00:14:59,230
- Dr. Oberman. - Dr. Oberman. Okay, and is he...? 

236
00:14:59,440 --> 00:15:01,983
- She. - Of course, "she."

237
00:15:02,776 --> 00:15:07,196
She, uh, familiar with our special situation?

238
00:15:07,406 --> 00:15:09,240
Yes, and she's very supportive.

239
00:15:09,450 --> 00:15:11,534
Great. Okay, that's great. Heh.

240
00:15:13,162 --> 00:15:14,704
No, I'm...

241
00:15:15,706 --> 00:15:17,165
CAROL: Thanks.

242
00:15:31,680 --> 00:15:32,889
Quack, quack...

243
00:15:33,098 --> 00:15:35,099
...quack, quack, quack.

244
00:15:35,309 --> 00:15:36,976
Ross?

245
00:15:37,311 --> 00:15:38,937
That opens my cervix.

246
00:15:45,778 --> 00:15:48,279
- Barry? BARRY: Come on in.

247
00:15:48,489 --> 00:15:49,447
Are you sure?

248
00:15:49,657 --> 00:15:52,116
BARRY: It's fine, it's fine. Robbie's gonna be here for hours.

249
00:15:52,326 --> 00:15:53,493
Huh?

250
00:15:56,705 --> 00:15:58,414
So how are you doing?

251
00:15:59,583 --> 00:16:01,250
I'm...

252
00:16:01,919 --> 00:16:03,753
I'm okay.

253
00:16:04,630 --> 00:16:05,797
You look great.

254
00:16:06,215 --> 00:16:07,256
Yeah, well...

255
00:16:08,008 --> 00:16:10,635
RECEPTIONIST [OVER SPEAKER]: Dr. Farber, Jason Greenspan's gagging.

256
00:16:10,844 --> 00:16:13,596
Be right there. I'll be back in a second.

257
00:16:18,686 --> 00:16:20,186
I dumped him.

258
00:16:21,522 --> 00:16:22,814
Okay.

259
00:16:31,365 --> 00:16:32,573
Oh!

260
00:16:37,496 --> 00:16:42,125
- Ross. - So, um...? So how's this going to work...

261
00:16:42,334 --> 00:16:43,918
...ahem, you know, with us?

262
00:16:44,128 --> 00:16:47,046
You know, when, like, important decisions have to be made?

263
00:16:47,423 --> 00:16:48,715
Give me a "for instance."

264
00:16:48,924 --> 00:16:50,591
Well, I don't know. Okay, okay.

265
00:16:50,801 --> 00:16:53,136
- How about with the baby's name? - Marlon...

266
00:16:53,345 --> 00:16:57,181
- Marlon. ...if it's a boy. Minnie, if it's a girl.

267
00:16:59,268 --> 00:17:00,893
As in "Mouse"?

268
00:17:02,438 --> 00:17:03,813
As in my grandmother.

269
00:17:04,690 --> 00:17:07,734
Still, you say "Minnie," you hear "Mouse."

270
00:17:09,820 --> 00:17:11,404
How about, um...

271
00:17:12,072 --> 00:17:13,489
How about "Julia"?

272
00:17:14,366 --> 00:17:15,408
Julia.

273
00:17:15,617 --> 00:17:16,784
We agreed on Minnie.

274
00:17:16,994 --> 00:17:19,746
It's funny, um, we agreed we'd spend our lives together.

275
00:17:19,997 --> 00:17:22,790
Things change. Roll with the punches.

276
00:17:23,333 --> 00:17:25,251
I believe Julia's on the table.

277
00:17:27,337 --> 00:17:29,714
Oh. Sorry about that.

278
00:17:32,926 --> 00:17:35,344
So, what have you been up to?

279
00:17:35,554 --> 00:17:38,421
Oh. Not much.

280
00:17:38,599 --> 00:17:41,392
- I got a job. - Hey, that's great. 

281
00:17:42,519 --> 00:17:43,936
Why are you so tan?

282
00:17:45,022 --> 00:17:46,189
Oh, I, uh...

283
00:17:46,899 --> 00:17:48,649
I went to Aruba.

284
00:17:48,984 --> 00:17:51,778
Oh, no. You went on our honeymoon alone?

285
00:17:51,987 --> 00:17:53,488
No.

286
00:17:55,407 --> 00:17:58,493
See, uh, I went with...

287
00:17:59,953 --> 00:18:01,412
- Now, this may hurt. - Me?

288
00:18:01,622 --> 00:18:02,872
No.

289
00:18:05,876 --> 00:18:06,959
I went with Mindy.

290
00:18:07,836 --> 00:18:09,462
Mindy?

291
00:18:10,047 --> 00:18:11,714
My maid of honor, Mindy?

292
00:18:11,924 --> 00:18:14,592
Yeah, well, we're kind of a thing now.

293
00:18:16,470 --> 00:18:18,012
Well, I'm...

294
00:18:19,139 --> 00:18:20,973
You got plugs.

295
00:18:21,183 --> 00:18:24,018
Careful, careful. They haven't quite taken yet.

296
00:18:24,645 --> 00:18:26,979
And you got lenses.

297
00:18:27,231 --> 00:18:29,899
But you hate sticking your finger in your eye.

298
00:18:30,109 --> 00:18:31,818
Not for her.

299
00:18:32,903 --> 00:18:34,070
Oh.

300
00:18:35,697 --> 00:18:38,074
Listen, I really wanted to thank you.

301
00:18:38,742 --> 00:18:40,159
Okay.

302
00:18:41,078 --> 00:18:42,995
About a month ago, I wanted to hurt you...

303
00:18:43,413 --> 00:18:45,790
...more than I've ever wanted to hurt anyone in my life.

304
00:18:45,999 --> 00:18:47,416
And I'm an orthodontist.

305
00:18:48,210 --> 00:18:49,710
Wow.

306
00:18:49,920 --> 00:18:53,506
You know, you were right. I mean, I thought we were happy.

307
00:18:53,715 --> 00:18:54,757
We weren't happy.

308
00:18:56,426 --> 00:18:58,261
But with Mindy...

309
00:18:59,138 --> 00:19:00,847
...now I'm happy.

310
00:19:02,182 --> 00:19:03,307
- Spit. - What?

311
00:19:03,517 --> 00:19:05,268
Me.

312
00:19:07,104 --> 00:19:09,480
Anyway, um...

313
00:19:10,482 --> 00:19:13,860
I guess, uh... I guess this belongs to you.

314
00:19:15,028 --> 00:19:17,488
And thank you for giving it to me.

315
00:19:18,115 --> 00:19:20,533
Well, thank you for giving it back.

316
00:19:24,037 --> 00:19:25,746
Hello.

317
00:19:29,042 --> 00:19:31,085
Oh, please. What's wrong with Helen?

318
00:19:31,295 --> 00:19:32,420
Helen Geller?

319
00:19:33,797 --> 00:19:37,216
- I don't think so. - Hello, it's not gonna be Helen Geller.

320
00:19:37,426 --> 00:19:38,801
Thank you.

321
00:19:39,011 --> 00:19:40,761
No. I mean, it's not Geller.

322
00:19:41,597 --> 00:19:43,055
What, it's gonna be Helen Willick?

323
00:19:43,765 --> 00:19:48,936
No, actually, um, we talked about Helen Willick Bunch.

324
00:19:50,147 --> 00:19:52,773
Well, wait a minute. Why is she in the title?

325
00:19:52,983 --> 00:19:54,358
Because it's my baby too.

326
00:19:54,568 --> 00:19:57,862
That's funny. Really? I don't remember you making any sperm.

327
00:20:00,574 --> 00:20:03,159
And we all know what a challenge that is.

328
00:20:03,368 --> 00:20:05,203
- Uh-huh. See? - All right, you two, stop it.

329
00:20:05,412 --> 00:20:07,747
No, no. She gets a credit. Hey, I'm in there too.

330
00:20:07,956 --> 00:20:11,918
Honestly. You're not actually suggesting Helen Willick Bunch Geller.

331
00:20:12,127 --> 00:20:13,711
I think that borders on child abuse.

332
00:20:13,921 --> 00:20:17,715
Of course not. I'm suggesting Geller Willick Bunch.

333
00:20:17,925 --> 00:20:20,384
Oh, no. No, no, no. You see what he's doing?

334
00:20:20,594 --> 00:20:22,428
He knows no one is gonna say all those names.

335
00:20:22,638 --> 00:20:25,264
He knows they'll wind up calling her Geller. Then he gets his way.

336
00:20:25,474 --> 00:20:27,683
My way? You think this is my way?

337
00:20:27,893 --> 00:20:31,437
Believe me, of all the ways I ever imagined this moment in my life being...

338
00:20:31,647 --> 00:20:34,857
...this is not my way. You know what? This is too hard.

339
00:20:35,067 --> 00:20:38,069
Knock, knock. How are we today? Any nausea?
340
00:20:38,278 --> 00:20:40,154
- A little. - Just a little.

341
00:20:41,949 --> 00:20:46,577
Well, I was just wondering about the mother-to-be, but, uh, thanks for sharing.

342
00:20:46,787 --> 00:20:47,870
Uh, lie back.

343
00:20:48,664 --> 00:20:50,289
You know what? I'm gonna go.

344
00:20:50,499 --> 00:20:54,502
Um, I don't think I can be involved in this particular family thing.

345
00:21:05,931 --> 00:21:07,348
Oh, my God.

346
00:21:07,557 --> 00:21:08,641
Look at that.

347
00:21:08,850 --> 00:21:10,309
I know.

348
00:21:21,071 --> 00:21:23,364
Well, isn't that amazing?

349
00:21:26,785 --> 00:21:28,494
What are we supposed to be seeing here?

350
00:21:30,330 --> 00:21:34,208
I don't know, but I think it's about to attack the Enterprise.

351
00:21:38,255 --> 00:21:41,173
You know, if you tilt your head to the left and relax your eyes...

352
00:21:41,383 --> 00:21:43,634
...it kind of looks like an old potato.

353
00:21:44,761 --> 00:21:47,054
Then don't do that, all right?

354
00:21:49,224 --> 00:21:50,474
Monica?

355
00:21:50,684 --> 00:21:52,226
What do you think?

356
00:21:52,436 --> 00:21:53,894
Mm-hm.

357
00:21:55,063 --> 00:21:56,522
Are you welling up?

358
00:21:56,732 --> 00:21:57,982
- No. - You are.

359
00:21:58,191 --> 00:22:00,443
- You are. You're welling up. - No, I'm not.

360
00:22:00,652 --> 00:22:03,779
- You're gonna be an aunt. - Oh, shut up.

361
00:22:04,948 --> 00:22:06,407
Hi, Mindy.

362
00:22:06,616 --> 00:22:08,701
Hi, it's Rachel.

363
00:22:08,910 --> 00:22:12,705
Yeah, I'm fine. I saw Barry today.

364
00:22:12,914 --> 00:22:14,582
Oh, yeah, yeah, he told me.

365
00:22:14,791 --> 00:22:17,501
No, it's okay. Really, it's okay.

366
00:22:17,711 --> 00:22:21,380
I hope you two are very happy. I really do.

367
00:22:21,590 --> 00:22:24,759
And, Min, you know, if everything works out...

368
00:22:24,968 --> 00:22:29,096
...and you guys end up getting married and having kids and everything...

369
00:22:29,306 --> 00:22:32,683
...I just hope they have his old hairline and your old nose.

370
00:22:37,731 --> 00:22:40,983
Okay, I know it was a cheap shot, but I feel so much better now.
